Everyone believes that if they work hard, their dreams will come true
But it's not such a sweet story
Even if you desperrayely aim high
Results are everything, I know that, but I don't understand it
Someday someone will see and believes
And I'll keep walking today too
The scenery visile
When on the verge of giving up or breaking down
Beyond the darkness
Of pain and despair
What awaits beyond the endless road
Even if it's far away, I will grab it with my hands
The shape of a dream different from the ideal
Continuing to pursue and struggle
Just moving forward
In our own hands now
We change the game from our own side
Living freely in a world
We have yet to see
Chiar dacă nu se potrivesc cu idealurile tale
Chase ambitions in your own way
Crap. I'm gonna die.
Give me a break.
I...
I'm supposed to become a
mithril-class adventurer!
Huh?
Wait, wait. This can't be happening.
This can't be happening!
Chiar dacă nu se potrivesc cu idealurile tale
Urmează-ți ambițiile în stilul tău
--------Aventurierul transformat într-un mort-viu--------
Recklessly chasing who I want to become
But before I knew it, I had become an adult
Episodul 1: Am transformat într-un mort-viu
The day starts early for adventurers.
Which sounds nice,
but the day starts early
for most poor people.
The only people who sleep until
noon are nobles, wealthy merchants,
and scholars living disorderly lives.
Maybe that's just my bias talking, though.
But my scholar friend sometimes forget
to sleep for days because they're
so focused on their research.
I should check in on them soon.
Either way, it's not something a
low bronze-class adventurer,
born and raised in a town
too small to be on the map,
Rentt Faina, knows anything about.
Okay.
There's one reason adventurers get up early,
and that's to get good jobs.
The adventurers' guild provides us with
jobs suitable for our rank and skills.
All manner of jobs are available,
such as monster extermination,
protection, herb and material gathering,
and even cleaning muck out of drains.
Hey, Rentt.
Good morning.
Are you going to the Labyrinth of
The Moon's Reflection again today?
If there aren't any good jobs.
How do you work so hard every day?
Well, see you later.
Good luck.
You, too.
Later.
Guess I'll go to the
Labyrinth of The Moon's Reflection.
Most adventurers form parties,
but I generally work solo.
There are a few reasons for that,
but mostly, it's because I'm not very good.
Even though I've been
adventuring for ten years,
I'm still only bronze,
the second lowest rank.
But even I can make a living
hunting monsters and selling magic
stones and materials to the guild.
Thank you. Come again.
Most of all, I live conscientiously
for an adventurer.
I've even got an emergency fund.
But in that moment, I lost my prudence
that's essential to all adventurers...
because in the thoroughly-explored
and completely deserted
Labyrinth of The Moon's Reflection,
I found something unbelievable.
Could it be?
A secret passageway?
What a discovery!
There's no mistaking it.
This is an unexplored area.
Maybe I'll find some valuable
magical equipment or weapons.
No, I could make a killing simply
reporting this news to the guild.
I should've ignored it,
but I went charging right into that
suspicious and dangerous place alone.
Because I'm a fool.
I found myself facing a dragon.
The greatest of all monsters.
A real dragon.
According to legend, they take many forms,
and some are considerably larger
than most standard dragons.
Regardless, I realized right away
that it was a dragon,
even though I'd never seen it before.
Its sheer presence—
the pressure it exerted that
froze me to the spot—
attested that it was a dragon.
As the thousand-year
bronze-class adventurer,
I stood no chance against
such an exceptional creature.
How am I alive after being eaten by a dragon?
No, wait. Am I actually alive?
I'm very obviously a skeleton.
I'm an immortal monster known as an undead,
but a bishop or priest could easily
destroy me with their purification magic
because undead violate
the divine providence
that the dead are not meant for this world.
When I think of it that way,
does that mean I died?
No, I'm still conscious and have my memories.
I should return to town.
No, I can't do that.
I don't want to die yet.
No, wait. I'm already dead,
so I don't want to be destroyed.
Oh, no! I'm confused!
An adventurer mustn't lose his head!
There's no point in thinking about
questions I can't answer right now.
The dragon seems to be gone,
but I should start by getting away from here.
These labyrinths can be
found around the world.
Many researches are trying
to explain their mysteries,
but no one really knows where
they come from or how they work.
Labyrinths come in various sizes,
but precious magical equipment and
treasures slumber within them,
and monsters can be found
around every corner.
Monsters are mysterious, as well.
Everyone's likely at the Labyrinth of the
New Moon where there's good money to be had.
In a few days, some solo adventurers
like me should come here.
I'll try asking them for advice.
Oh!
First I need to figure out
how I'll talk to them.
Huh?
My body feels heavy.
Maybe because I have no muscles,
my physical abilities are significantly worse.
I'm even less capable
than an ordinary person.
That's to be expected.
After all, I'm a skeleton now.
I could defeat them easily as a human,
but I need to be careful now.
I can't raise my sword!
That's not good!
I shouldn't expect to use fancy sword
techniques when I'm made of bones.
But what about my other abilities?
All living things draw on their
vital energy for strength.
Their spirit energy.
It's working.
Right now, you and I are the same.
Our strength is equal.
But my equipment gives me an advantage.
If I use my spirit energy to buff my
physical abilities and raise my attack power...
Is it still alive?
I'm recovering the spirit
energy I just expended?
Could it be?
Monsters have a mysterious trait.
With time and experience,
they evolve into greater beings.
So do humans.
We grow with training.
They're on another level.
For example, a skeleton is
typically a skeleton forever.
But on rare occasions,
they evolve into ghouls.
It's known as
existential evolution.
Existential evolution...
Yes. It's one of the
subjects I'm researching.
Existential evolution, huh?
Ghouls are also undead, but they
have flesh and are closer to humans.
If I use robes and masks to hide my form,
I may be able to return to town.
All right. I should aim to achieve
existential evolution first.
I'll defeat monsters in this
labyrinth and become a ghoul.
He didn't come today, either.
Oh, well.
I'll make dinner myself.
That's five!
My mobility has been mostly restored.
Anyway, it seems like this light heals me.
Because of it, I can use spirit
energy during every battle.
I'll try taking on some
stronger monsters next.
Like skeletons, slimes are
an archetypal weak monster,
but they mustn't be underestimated.
Physical attacks are less effective
against amorphous liquid monsters.
Magic is the easy way to beat them,
but unfortunately, I don't have the
ability to use offensive magic.
The most I can do is start fires
suitable for domestic tasks.
So I'll have to use physical
attacks to defeat it.
There are two ways to do it.
Pierce its core, or break apart its
liquid form until it can't regenerate.
Lacking in both skill and strength,
once a day I can expend my reserves
of spirit energy to defeat them.
You could say slimes are my greatest enemy.
Huh?
Looks like I got lucky and
my blade struck its core.
First I'll retrieve its magic stone.
Slimes have the ability
to launch an Acid Blitz,
but no acid remains in their
body once they're dead.
In fact, sticking your hand in
the stuff makes your skin smooth.
Clear slime fluids are used
to make cosmetics for women.
Surely we don't have to make
cosmetics out of monsters.
Women's desire for beauty must be endless.
This'll pay for several days at an inn.
Good.
Take care.
Sheila.
Yes?
Has that newbie found a party yet?
Her letter of introduction said
she lacks combat experience,
but she seems all right with a sword.
There wasn't a suitable opening for them,
so I was going to ask Rentt,
but he hasn't been back since yesterday.
That's unusual.
He hasn't accepted a long-term job, has he?
No, nothing that would take him out of Maalt.
I told the newbie I'd introduce her to a
helpful veteran if she waited a few days,
but she seemed pressed for money,
so I told her about the
Labyrinth of The Moon's Reflection.
That should be fine.
Even a newbie should be able to handle it,
if they're decent with a sword.
Right. I did warn her
not to overdo it, though.
I don't feel sleepy at all,
and I don't feel hungry, either.
I guess that's obvious since I'm undead.
Anything I ate would probably
fall to the ground.
I fought all night since I might as well,
but it seems like existential
evolution takes longer than that.
My physical abilities were significantly
worse right after I became a skeleton,
but I'm mostly back to normal
after defeating those monsters.
I tested my spirit energy,
and it still works.
I can use my mana, too.
I can even use my divinity
despite being undead.
I don't want to waste it.
I'll use it on this bread.
In addition to curing injuries and illnesses,
divinity is a useful power that can
purify water and delay spoiling in food.
Okay. That should make
it last three more days.
I hope I'll have a body that
needs bread three days from now.
There's no point in thinking about it.
I should focus on achieving
existential evolution.
I'll play it safe for a while
and steadily defeat monsters.
I can beat one or two.
Three would be difficult.
If I encounter four, I'll run.
And more than five...
It's unlikely I'll encounter groups
that large in this labyrinth,
but if I do, I'm screwed.
That would be the end of me.
I'm so weak.
It's been ten years since
I became an adventurer.
If you include my training time
before that, it's been twenty years.
Not only that, but even
high-ranking adventurers rarely
have spirit energy, mana, and divinity.
I wish I had just one strong power.
I know I'm not cut out to be an adventurer.
Normally, people give up on
adventuring after a few years
and return to their village
to farm or find another job.
But I figured as long as I'm alive,
I'd manage somehow.
I trained every day without fail.
I asked an acquaintance to teach
me about monsters and magic.
I accepted even the most minor jobs.
I did that for ten years to achieve my dream.
To become a mithril-class adventurer.
Higher than gold- and platinum-class,
not even naturally gifted people
easily reach the highest rank
of adventurers who have saved entire nations.
I will become mithril-class.
It's what I've lived for.
Becoming a skeleton won't stop me!
Huh?
I'm starting to get stronger
than I was as a human?
I knew it.
It's not a coincidence.
I'm getting stronger.
I can sell these materials.
I should gather some more.
I'm lucky to acquire more clear slime fluid.
Slimes are fairly gross after
they've eaten something,
so their fluids can't be sold.
Wha— What's happening?
I'm a ghoul.
I'm a creepy dried-out corpse,
but I have flesh.
This is major progress.
If I keep working hard, I might be able
to become even higher ranking undead.
That's right.
Vampires practically look human.
Oh, right. I have a fleshy body now.
Okay, I can make noises.
Salut... salut...
Good morning...
Va trebui să exersez.
Salut... salut...
Eu sunt Rentt...
QWERTYUIOPASA
SADASDASDFFHEV
Data viitoare
Începătoarea și veteranul
Incepatoarea si veteranul